Chi Jia,
what's going on?
Check this out.
Let me see.
[Dear Xu Anbo,]
[congratulations on your work,]
[Arena Light and Shadow,]
[being shortlisted for our]
[photography collection.]
[We sincerely invite you]
to attend an offline exchange
this weekend.
What's going on?
Lin Qingyuan and I submitted it for you.
Lin Qingyuan?
He knew you wanted to enter
but couldn't let go of the basketball game.
He didn't want you to miss out,
so he came to me in secret
and chose a few of your photos
to submit.
Why didn't he tell me?
He's afraid you won't be selected.
And you'll be disappointed.
We made a deal.
If you're selected, he'll tell you.
If not, he'll pretend nothing happened.
So he insisted on being in the starting lineup
to give me a chance.
It took you a while to figure it out.
If you're selected,
you'll miss the game.
If you're just a substitute,
the pressure is less.
That's what Lin Qingyuan thinks.
He's just
acting like a fool.
And you two are arguing with him.
You're also fools.
Brother,
are you going to
the event this weekend?
Lin Qingyuan,
my work has been shortlisted.
Thank you.
Really?
Congratulations!
I'm sorry
to make you
have a fight with them.
But actually,
Xu Anbo,
it was me
who invited you to join the club.
You've been working hard
to pursue our dream.
This time,
I hope
you can pursue your dream.
Lin Qingyuan,
thank you.
But the next game is crucial.
I insist on being a starter
Because
I believe you will make it.
Do you believe we will win?
I believe in you.
That's how it is.
I decided to attend
an offline fieldwork event this weekend.
If I become
a member of the photography team,
I will focus on photography
in my spare time.
If it's a problem for you,
I can quit the basketball club.
Sorry.
I see.
That's a good thing.
Yeah, bro.
I knew you were good at photography.
Now you're getting professional recognition.
We should support you.
Right?
You got in with
our basketball club's photos.
It's an honor for all of us.
Go ahead.
There's always a spot for you
in the Yibei Basketball Club.
You're really okay with this?
No worries.
But the next game is so important.
Gu Chenyang,
Fu Binyan has been preparing for so long.
and I just quit.
Even if you stay for the competition,
your heart isn't in it.
You might as well let you go.
Don't worry.
Xue Yihui has been practicing well this week.
He can take your place.
Right.
Okay.
One more thing.
Lin Qingyuan...
Did you hear me?
Come in.
Lin Qingyuan,
I was wrong about you that day.
I'm sorry.
Well,
I was wrong too.
Me too.
Actually,
that day,
I was also at fault.
So we're even.
Great.
Our team spirit is back.
Can Lin Qingyuan
play in the next game?
I took him to the infirmary
this afternoon.
He can play on Saturday.
But
I still want him to be
our sixth man.
Here.
Hello.
There are really
a lot of people here today.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
Is it because it's stuffy here
or because I'm nervous?
Feel it.
Here.
It's fine.
Are you okay?
Why are you nervous?
Don't make him
nervous.
How about
I go back and you two watch?
No way.
No.
We're here
to cheer for Xiaoyu.
Aren't you two nervous?
Uncle,
just sit back and relax.
Xu Anbo won't be here today,
and Li Haoyu told us
to take more photos.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll leave it to you.
Alright,
give me something to do.
to distract me.
If you don't take good pictures,
he'll throw a fit again.
Isn't this green one open?
Why is it black?
Don't be nervous, Li.
Okay, it's lit.
Come on,
let me take a picture of you two first.
Come on.
One, two, three.
Lin Hai.
This stadium is huge.
So many people.
It should be almost time, right?
Is it?
Where do we sit?
Over there, over there.
Those two.
These two.
Right, right, right.
Okay.
Hello, sir and ma'am.
Hello.
I'm Jiang Yi,
Qingyuan's senior.
Nice to meet you.
Xiaoyi, this is
Qingyuan's parents,
and this is Haoyu's parents.
Nice to meet you.
Hello, Mr. Li.
You look so young.
Hello, Mrs. Li.
You had a baby at a young age.
Yeah.
We had a baby at a young age.
You all like outdoor activities.
You even bring a telescope.
Yeah.
We like road trips.
We'll leave
once our son's
game's over.
That's so chill!
Going on a trip right away?
Yeah,
a victory tour!
Come on,
have a seat.
Come on, sit down.
Slow down.
I'm fine.
Yibei, go for it!
Here we go!
No. 3 Middle School, who can rival us?
They're really pumped!
Let's cheer
for our kids too!
Yibei, fearless in youth!
Shout with me!
Okay.
Yibei, fearless in youth!
The game is about to start.
Wait for my good news.
Yibei, fearless in youth!
Why is Yuan still wearing a jacket?
I wanted to ask you.
Isn't he in the starting lineup?
Yibei, fearless in youth!
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I just feel
you've become much more composed lately.
Of course.
Everyone has to grow up, right?
[Ladies and gentlemen,]
[welcome to the live broadcast]
[of Group A of the national high school]
[basketball tournament.]
[Today's match-up]
[is between Yibei Middle School and Fanghe No.3 Middle School.]
[As you can see,]
[today,]
[Yibei Middle School]
[has made some lineup changes.]
[They've brought in the newcomer Chen Song]
[to replace point guard Lin Qingyuan,]
[and bench center Zhu Zhan]
[to replace Xu Anbo.]
[Let's all look forward to]
[this new lineup's performance.]
Nice shot!
Defense!
Hold the line!
Yibei, keep it up!
[The opening period]
[has been dominated by Fanghe No. 3's]
[star center,]
[showcasing his skills.]
[On the other side,]
[their new lineup]
[is clearly not]
[fully coordinated.]
[Yibei Middle School is behind by nine points.]
Help defense!
Hurry up!
Get the rebound!
Block him!
Don't let him have it so easily!
No. 3 Middle School, who can rival us?
Fu Binyan,
is the current situation
what you expected?
Yes.
But,
it's not the most favorable outcome I anticipated.
Should I go on the court?
Wait a bit.
Your shoulder injury isn't fully healed yet.
It's not the right time.
Okay.
I believe in you.
What should we do?
When is Yuan going to play?
I'm so anxious.
Look for yourself.
I said he was not in the right state.
Normally, he would have been anxious by now.
Why is he so steady today?
Honey.
I suddenly feel
Yuan has grown up a bit.
Coach,
I think it's enough.
What do you think?
Let them get ready
to warm up.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Yibei Middle School requests a substitution.
We can see
Lin Qingyuan is about to enter the game.
Can he work with the players on the field
[with the current players?]
[Let's wait and see.]
Xiaoyuan's in.
Xiaoyuan, go for it!
Nice!
Why can't Lin Qingyuan
start in the lineup?
Because Fang He's post player
has a big advantage.
We may fall behind
in the starting lineup,
but it doesn't matter.
As long as we keep the score close,
when the opposing center's stamina drops,
that's when we counterattack.
Lin Qingyuan's defense is weak,
but his offense is strong.
He's the best card to play
at that time,
our secret weapon.
Okay.
Then I'll be the secret weapon.
[No. 77 from Yibei,]
[Lin Qingyuan, is going for a layup.]
[No. 29 from Fanghe,]
[Zeng Qinglong, collides with him.]
[He falls hard on his right shoulder.]
[Foul on defense.]
[Medical staff enter the court.]
[Yibei team's]
[No. 77 player is injured and leaves the game.]
[Half-time break.]
Xiaoyuan.
How do you feel?
It hurts so much, my son.
Brother Lin, Sister Ye.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
You call this fine?
You were lying there motionless just now.
You scared me to death.
Coach, why did that person
have to hit him?
I'm fine.
Just need some ice.
It's already swollen.
Coach,
what's the score now?
It's the fourth quarter.
Gu Chenyang, Li Haoyu,
Zhou Yang, and Chen Song are all on the court.
The opponent's post is so strong.
They're all holding on.
How much is the score now?
Don't worry about that now.
Yeah.
Why do you care about that?
Your arm is swollen.
The score must be far apart.
No.
I must go.
You can't even lift your hand.
Why do you go?
Be gentle.
Well...
I've used ice
and taken medicine.
I can do this.
How can you do this?
You used to cry for ages
over a minor bump.
How can you do this now?
Mom,
I'm not a little kid anymore.
Besides,
I'm about to be a big brother.
I'm all grown up.
Coach,
I can do this.
Let me play.
Coach, he...
Let him watch from the sidelines for now.
We'll see.
Alright.
Brother Lin.
Sister Ye.
I have to play in this game.
[With three minutes left,]
[Yibei is still five points behind.]
[For both teams,]
[this is a must-win game.]
[A loss here]
[means elimination.]
[Everyone on the court]
[is giving it their all.]
[Who will be]
[the final winner?]
[Let's find out!]
Coach, let me play.
Trust me.
[Lin Qingyuan from Yibei]
[insists on returning to the court.]
[Can he really hold on?]
[This is so unexpected.]
Go for it!
Are you sure your hand's okay?
It's fine.
Trust me.
Go for it!
[Yuan's back in the game.]
[Fanghe No.3 Middle School, No. 29.]
[Foul.]
[Two points and a free throw.]
[With three seconds left in the game,]
[Lin Qingyuan steps up to the free throw line]
[to score the crucial two points.]
[The score is tied.]
[This free throw]
[will decide the outcome.]
[Can Lin Qingyuan overcome the pain]
[and score another point?]
[Let's wait and see.]
Defense!
[The game is over.]
[Yibei has won.]
[Despite facing]
[numerous challenges,]
[they never gave up.]
[fearlessly facing strong opponents,]
[and overcoming pain.]
[With a perfect comeback,]
[they've shown the team's]
[resilience and determination.]
[The victory is theirs.]
Yibei! Yibei!
Bro, we won the game!
Yibei, victory is ours!
Honey,
our son won!
and made it to the knockout round.
So boring.
Wait a minute.
When I came an hour ago,
you were looking at this picture.
I'm just studying it.
It's not right.
Let me study it.
I'm studying it.
Honey,
why are you still the same?
You're getting older,
but still arguing with our son
and refusing to go to the scene.
And what's the result?
You sneakily
hide here to watch the live broadcast.
Who watched it?
I...
I'm just clearing my mind.
I... I just took a quick glance.
I didn't watch it.
Go back to your work.
Go back inside.
I won't disturb you
enjoying yourself alone.
Who's enjoying themselves?
What's there to enjoy?
I...
I'm not...
Hello,
I'm Gu Chenyang's father.
Yeah, yeah.
Gu Chenyang,
from Yibei Middle School's basketball team.
So,
about what we discussed last time,
can we move forward with it?